Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Newsprint Comic Strips RL.11749
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Newspaper comic sections (Funnies), 1925-1988; 2
  - New Orleans Times Picayune, 1949-1950
    Comic strips include: Peter Rabbit, They'll Do It Every Time, Portrait in Bullets (RJ Reynolds advertisements), Captain Easy, Casey Ruggles, Rusty Riley, Annie Rooney, Toonerville Folks, Steve Canyon, Nancy, Ella Cinders, Off the Record, Right Around Home, Prince Valiant, Bringing Up Father, Tillie the Toiler, Dixie Dugan, Red Ryder, Kerry Drake, American Adventure, Mark Trail, Uncle Remus, Little Iodine, Joe Palooka, Mandrake the Magician, Mickey Finn, Napoleon, Ripley's Believe it or Not, Vignettes of Life, Blondie, Fritzi Ritz, Lil' Abner, The Katzendammer Kids, Colonel Potterby and the Dutchess.
    - New Orleans Times Picayune comics sections, 1949-1950 (Box 21)
  - The News and Observer, 1934-1936, 1949-1952
    (Raleigh, N.C.) Includes Alexander Smart ESQ, And So They Were Never Married, Babe n'Horace, Belles and Wedding Bells, Blondie, Boots, Boulder Dam, Bringing Up Father, Buz Sawyer, Captain Easy, Carnival, Chris Crusty, Colonel Potter, The Comic Zoo, Ella Cinders, Family Foursom, Flashing Foils, The Gumps, Henry, Jane Arden, Kitty Higgins, Li'l Abner, Moon Mullins, Mr. Hale Lends a Hand, Mr. Merry Whether, Otto Honk, Out Our Way, The Phantom, Penny, Polly and Her Pals, Prince Valiant, Rosie's Beau, Smilin' Jack, Tarzan, and Steve Canyon
    - The News and Observer, 1934-1935 (Box 101)
    - The News and Observer, 1935 (Box 101)
    - The News and Observer, 1935-1936 (Box 101)
    - The News and Observer, 1949-1952 (Box 94)
    - The News and Observer, 1952 (Box 94)
  - The Overseas Weekly, 1972-1977
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1972 Aug-Oct (Box 65)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1972 Jul (Box 65)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1972 Oct-Nov (Box 64)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1972 Dec-1973 Feb (Box 64)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1973 Feb-Mar (Box 64)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1973 Jul-Aug (Box 63)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1973 May-Jul (Box 63)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1973 Oct-Nov (Box 63)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1973 Dec-1974 Feb (Box 61)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1974 Apr-Aug (Box 61)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1974 Sep-Dec (Box 61)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1975 Apr-Jul (Box 62)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1975 Jan-Mar (Box 62)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1975 Jul-Sep (Box 62)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1975 Sep-Nov (Box 66)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1975 Dec-1976 Jul (Box 66)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1976 Aug-Oct (Box 66)
    - The Overseas Weekly, 1976-1977 Nov-Jan (Box 65)
  - Public Opinion Comic Sections, 1935-1936; scattered (Box 60)
  - Star Weekly Comic Collection, 1954-1955 (Box 83)
  - Stars and Stripes, 1945-1949
    - Stars and Stripes Mediterranian Comics, 1945 Feb-Oct; scattered (Box 60)
    - Stars and Stripes Pacific Far East Weekly Review, 1947-1949; scattered (Box 60)
    - Stars and Stripes Pacific Features, 1946 Mar-Jul; scattered (Box 60)
    - Stars and Stripes Pacific Features and Comics, 1945-1946; scattered (Box 60)
  - Sunday Telegraph, 1944 Sep-1945 Oct (Box 94)
    Includes Ambrose Kangaroo, Brick Bradford, Henry, Nancy, Superman, The Katzenjammer Kids, The Little King, The Pussycat Princess, Wanda the War Girl
  - The Washington Post, 1973-1988
    - The Washington Post, 1972; scattered (Box 1)
    - The Washington Post, 1973 Aug-Sep. (Box 2)
      Aug. and Oct. 1973 are incomplete.
    - The Washington Post, 1973 Nov.-1974 Mar (Box 3)
      Nov. 1973 is incomplete.
    - The Washington Post, 1974 Apr-Sept (Box 4)
      July and Aug. 1974 are incomplete.
    - The Washington Post, 1974 Oct-1975 Feb (Box 5)
    - The Washington Post, 1975 Mar-July (Box 6)
    - The Washington Post, 1975 Aug-1976 Feb, Apr., Jun-July (Box 7)
      Sept.-Dec. 1975 issues are incomplete. Feb. and April 1976 are incomplete.
    - The Washington Post, 1976 Aug-1977 Oct (Box 8)
    - The Washington Post, 1977 Nov-Dec., 1978, 1979, 1981 Aug (Box 9)
      1978, 1979, and Aug. 1981 issues are incomplete.
    - The Washington Post, 1977 Sep-1978 Dec (Box 10)
    - The Washington Post, 1974 July 21, 1974 Oct-1976 Mar (Box 11)
      Skips Dec. 14 and Dec. 28, 1975.
    - The Washington Post, 1976 Apr-1977 Aug, 1979 Jan-Mar (Box 12)
    - The Washington Post, 1979 Apr-1980 Aug (Box 13)
    - The Washington Post, 1980 Sep-1982 Feb (Box 14)
    - The Washington Post, 1982 Mar-1983 Jun (Box 15)
      Skips Jan. 16 1983. Dec. 5, 1982 and Apr. 25, 1982 are damaged.
    - The Washington Post, 1983 Jun-1984 Oct (Box 16)
      July 3 1983 and Oct. 16 1983 are damaged. Skips July 15, July 8, June 10, June 3, May 13, Apr. 1, Apr. 8, Apr. 15, Mar. 4, and Feb. 26, 1984. Also skips Dec. 11, 1983.
    - The Washington Post, 1984 Nov-1986 Feb (Box 17)
      skips Jan. 12, 1986; July 21 and Jan. 13, 1985; and Nov. 25, 1984.
    - The Washington Post, 1986 Feb-1987 May (Box 18)
      skips Mar. 23, Dec. 20, Nov. 23, Oct. 19, Sep. 20, July 27, July 6, June 30, and June 1 1986.
    - The Washington Post, 1987 May-1988 Jun (Box 19)
      skips Sept. 20, Aug. 2, July 19, July 26 1987.
  - Miscellaneous, 1933-1986 (Box 101)
    Mostly single-issue comic sections from various newspapers, many missing the title of the newspaper. One comic section was published in Mexico in 1986 and is in Spanish.